EDMONT KAMBERI

Gazmend Zajmi, Prishtina

Edmontkamberi15@gmail.com

048159207

15.07.1994, Gjilan RKS

OBJECTIVE

Enthusiastic and devoted English Language Student with excellent communication skills demonstrated. High degree of fluency in English Language and Albanian, partly Macedonian and Serbian; specialized in managing students and maximizing learning opportunities in diverse classroom settings.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Good command of Microsoft Innovative lesson planning Office family programs (Word, Learning style assessment PowerPoint, Excel)
Differentiated instruction, Team working abilities, Patience with children, Effectively work with students, Ability to handle 20–30students, Interactive teaching in a classroom, Able to discipline in multiple, Problem solving abilities ways and conditions, Critical Thinking, Skills Creativity in teaching lessons Instructional best practices.

EXPERIENCE

SALES AGENT, CHAT SUPPORT SPECIALIST, HR,

DEC. 2016 - JUL 2018 IN MEDIA BUY SERVICES

HOTEL MANAGER AND RECEPTIONIST

JUN 2020 – OCT 2020 - HOTEL PRESHEVA, ULCINJ JUN 2021 – OCT 2021 - HOTEL PRESHEVA, ULCINJ

INFINITY VISA AGENCY (OWNER)

JAN. 2022 - OCT. 2024 owner

EDUCATION

ENGLISH LANGUAGE PREPARATION SCHOOL

INTERNATIONAL BALKAN UNIVERISTY – SKOPJE 2020 – 2021

ENGLISH LANGUAGE AND AMERICAN STUDIES (BA)

INTERNATIONAL BALKAN UNIVERISTY – SKOPJE 2013 – 2016

ENGLISH LANGUAGE (MA)

AAB UNIVERSITY – PRISHTINA Ongoing

COMMUNICATION

Presented embassy concepts and proposals to high-profile clients, receiving excellent feedback for clear, engaging presentations.

LEADERSHIP

Served as the lead Embassy consulator for over 4 high-profile countries in Balkans, mentoring candidate process and guiding the effective process from concept to completion.

LANGUAGES

Albanian Language, native
English Language , Advanced
Serbian, partial